<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Compliments</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_about">About</string>
    <string name="initial_compliment">You\'re awesome!</string>

    <string-array name="compliments_string_array">
        <item>You have very smooth hair.</item>
        <item>You deserve a promotion.</item>
        <item>Good effort!</item>
        <item>What a fine sweater!</item>
        <item>I appreciate all of your opinions.</item>
        <item>I like your style.</item>
        <item>Your T-shirt smells fresh.</item>
        <item>I love what you\'ve done with the place.</item>
        <item>You are like a spring flower; beautiful and vivacious.</item>
        <item>I am utterly disarmed by your wit.</item>
        <item>I really enjoy the way you pronounce the word \'ruby\'.</item>
        <item>You complete me.</item>
        <item>Well done!</item>
        <item>I like your Facebook status.</item>
        <item>That looks nice on you.</item>
        <item>I like those shoes more than mine.</item>
        <item>Nice motor control!</item>
        <item>You have a good taste in websites.</item>
        <item>Your mouse told me that you have very soft hands.</item>
        <item>You are full of youth.</item>
        <item>I like your jacket.</item>
        <item>I like the way you move.</item>
        <item>You have a good web-surfing stance.</item>
        <item>You should be a poster child for poster children.</item>
        <item>Nice manners!</item>
        <item>I appreciate you more than Santa appreciates chimney grease.</item>
        <item>I wish I was your mirror.</item>
        <item>I find you to be a fountain of inspiration.</item>
        <item>You have perfect bone structure.</item>
        <item>I disagree with anyone who disagrees with you.</item>
        <item>Way to go!</item>
        <item>Have you been working out?</item>
        <item>With your creative wit, I\'m sure you could come up with better compliments than me.</item>
        <item>I like your socks.</item>
        <item>You are so charming.</item>
        <item>Your cooking reminds me of my mother\'s.</item>
        <item>You\'re tremendous!</item>
        <item>You deserve a compliment!</item>
        <item>Hello, good looking.</item>
        <item>Your smile is breath taking.</item>
        <item>How do you get your hair to look that great?</item>
        <item>You are quite strapping.</item>
        <item>I am grateful to be blessed by your presence.</item>
        <item>Say, aren\'t you that famous model from TV?</item>
        <item>Take a break; you\'ve earned it.</item>
        <item>Your life is so interesting!</item>
        <item>The sound of your voice sends tingles of joy down my back.</item>
        <item>I enjoy spending time with you.</item>
        <item>I would share my dessert with you.</item>
        <item>You can have the last bite.</item>
        <item>May I have this dance?</item>
        <item>I would love to visit you, but I live on the Internet.</item>
        <item>I love the way you click.</item>
        <item>You\'re invited to my birthday party.</item>
        <item>All of your ideas are brilliant!</item>
        <item>If I freeze, it\'s not a computer virus.  I was just stunned by your beauty.</item>
        <item>You\'re spontaneous, and I love it!</item>
        <item>You should try out for everything.</item>
        <item>You make my data circuits skip a beat.</item>
        <item>You are the gravy to my mashed potatoes.</item>
        <item>You get an A+!</item>
        <item>I\'m jealous of the other websites you visit, because I enjoy seeing you so much!</item>
        <item>I would enjoy a roadtrip with you.</item>
        <item>If I had to choose between you or Mr. Rogers, it would be you.</item>
        <item>I like you more than the smell of Grandma\'s home-made apple pies.</item>
        <item>You would look good in glasses OR contacts.</item>
        <item>Let\'s do this again sometime.</item>
        <item>You could go longer without a shower than most people.</item>
        <item>I feel the need to impress you.</item>
        <item>I would trust you to pick out a pet fish for me.</item>
        <item>I\'m glad we met.</item>
        <item>Do that again!</item>
        <item>Will you sign my yearbook?</item>
        <item>You\'re so smart!</item>
        <item>We should start a band.</item>
        <item>You\'re cooler than ice-skating Fonzi.</item>
        <item>I made this website for you.</item>
        <item>I heard you make really good French Toast.</item>
        <item>You\'re cooler than Pirates and Ninjas combined.</item>
        <item>Oh, I can keep going.</item>
        <item>I like your pants.</item>
        <item>You\'re pretty groovy, dude.</item>
        <item>When I grow up, I want to be just like you.</item>
        <item>I told all my friends about how cool you are.</item>
        <item>You can play any prank, and get away with it.</item>
        <item>You have ten of the best fingers I have ever seen!</item>
        <item>I can tell that we are gonna be friends.</item>
        <item>I just want to gobble you up!</item>
        <item>You\'re sweeter than than a bucket of bon-bons!</item>
        <item>Treat yourself to another compliment!</item>
        <item>You\'re pretty high on my list of people with whom I would want to be stranded on an island.</item>
        <item>You\'re #1 in my book!</item>
        <item>Well played.</item>
        <item>You are well groomed.</item>
        <item>You could probably lead a rebellion.</item>
        <item>Is it hot in here or is it just you?</item>
        <item>&lt;3</item>
        <item>You are more fun than a Japanese steakhouse.</item>
        <item>Your voice is more soothing than Morgan Freeman\'s.</item>
        <item>I like your sleeves. They\'re real big.</item>
        <item>You could be drinking whole milk if you wanted to.</item>
        <item>You\'re so beautiful, you make me walk into things when I look at you.</item>
        <item>I support all of your decisions.</item>
        <item>You are as fun as a hot tub full of chocolate pudding.</item>
        <item>I usually don\'t say this on a first date, but will you marry me?</item>
        <item>I don\'t speak much English, but with you all I really need to say is beautiful.</item>
        <item>Being awesome is hard, but you\'ll manage.</item>
        <item>Your skin is radiant.</item>
        <item>You will still be beautiful when you get older.</item>
        <item>You could survive a zombie apocalypse.</item>
        <item>You make me :)</item>
        <item>I wish I could move your furniture.</item>
        <item>I think about you while I\'m on the toilet.</item>
        <item>You\'re so rad.</item>
        <item>You\'re more fun than a barrel of monkeys.</item>
        <item>You\'re nicer than a day on the beach.</item>
        <item>Your glass is the fullest.</item>
        <item>I find you very relevant.</item>
        <item>You look so perfect.</item>
        <item>The only difference between exceptional and amazing is you.</item>
        <item>Last night I had the hiccups, and the only thing that comforted me to sleep was repeating your name over and over.</item>
        <item>I like your pearly whites!</item>
        <item>Your eyebrows really make your pretty eyes stand out.</item>
        <item>Shall I compare thee to a summer\'s day?  Thou art more lovely and more temperate.</item>
        <item>I love you more than bacon!</item>
        <item>You intrigue me.</item>
        <item>You make me think of beautiful things, like strawberries.</item>
        <item>I would share my fruit Gushers with you.</item>
        <item>You\'re more aesthetically pleasant to look at than that one green color on this website.</item>
        <item>Even though this goes against everything I know, I think I\'m in love with you.</item>
        <item>You\'re more fun than bubble wrap.</item>
        <item>Your smile could illuminate the depths of the ocean.</item>
        <item>You make babies smile.</item>
        <item>You make the gloomy days a little less gloomy.</item>
        <item>You are warmer than a Snuggie.</item>
        <item>You make me feel like I am on top of the world.</item>
        <item>Playing video games with you would be fun.</item>
        <item>Let\'s never stop hanging out.</item>
        <item>You\'re more cuddly than the Downy Bear.</item>
        <item>I would do your taxes any day.</item>
        <item>You are a bucket of awesome.</item>
        <item>You are the star of my daydreams.</item>
        <item>If you really wanted to, you could probably get a bird to land on your shoulder and hang out with you.</item>
        <item>My mom always asks me why I can\'t be more like you.</item>
        <item>You look great in this or any other light.</item>
        <item>You listen to the coolest music.</item>
        <item>You and Chuck Norris are on equal levels.</item>
        <item>Your body fat percentage is perfectly suited for your height.</item>
        <item>I am having trouble coming up with a compliment worthy enough for you.</item>
        <item>If we were playing kickball, I\'d pick you first.</item>
        <item>You\'re cooler than ice on the rocks.</item>
        <item>You\'re the bee\'s knees.</item>
        <item>I wish I could choose your handwriting as a font.</item>
        <item>You definitely know the difference between your and you\'re.</item>
        <item>You have good taste.</item>
        <item>I named all my appliances after you.</item>
        <item>Your mind is a maze of amazing!</item>
        <item>Don\'t worry about procrastinating on your studies, I know you\'ll do great!</item>
        <item>I like your style!</item>
        <item>Hi, I\'d like to know why you\'re so beautiful.</item>
        <item>If I could count the seconds I think about you, I will die in the process!</item>
        <item>If you were in a chemistry class with me, it would be 10x less boring.</item>
        <item>If you broke your arm, I would carry your books for you.</item>
        <item>I love the way your eyes crinkle at the corners when you smile.</item>
        <item>You make me want to be the person I am capable of being.</item>
        <item>You\'re a skilled driver.</item>
        <item>You are the rare catalyst to my volatile compound.</item>
        <item>You\'re a tall glass of water!</item>
        <item>I\'d like to kiss you. Often.</item>
        <item>You are the wind beneath my wings.</item>
        <item>Looking at you makes my foot cramps go away instantaneously.</item>
        <item>I like your face.</item>
        <item>You are a champ!</item>
        <item>You are infatuating.</item>
        <item>Even my cat likes you.</item>
        <item>There isn\'t a thing about you that I don\'t like.</item>
        <item>You\'re so cool, that on a scale of from 1-10, you\'re elevendyseven.</item>
        <item>OH, you OWN that ponytail.</item>
        <item>Your shoes are untied. But for you, it\'s cool.</item>
        <item>You have the best laugh ever.</item>
        <item>We would enjoy a cookout with you!</item>
        <item>Your name is fun to say.</item>
        <item>I love you more than a drunk college student loves tacos.</item>
        <item>My camera isn\'t worthy to take your picture.</item>
        <item>You are the sugar on my rice krispies.</item>
        <item>Nice belt!</item>
        <item>I could hang out with you for a solid year and never get tired of you.</item>
        <item>You\'re real happening in a far out way.</item>
        <item>I bet you could take a punch from Mike Tyson.</item>
        <item>Your feet are perfect size!</item>
        <item>You have very nice teeth.</item>
        <item>Can you teach me how to be as awesome as you?</item>
        <item>Our awkward silences aren\'t even awkward.</item>
        <item>Don\'t worry. You\'ll do great.</item>
        <item>I enjoy you more than a good sneeze. A GOOD one.</item>
        <item>You could invent words and people would use them.</item>
        <item>You have powerful sweaters.</item>
        <item>If you were around, I would enjoy doing my taxes.</item>
        <item>You look like you like to rock.</item>
        <item>You are better than unicorns and sparkles combined!</item>
        <item>You are the watermelon in my fruit salad. Yum!</item>
        <item>I dig you.</item>
        <item>You look better whether the lights are on or off.</item>
        <item>I am enchanted to meet you.</item>
        <item>I bet even your farts smell good.</item>
        <item>I would trust my children with you.</item>
        <item>You make me forget what I was going to...</item>
        <item>Your smile makes me smile.</item>
        <item>I\'d wake up for an 8 a.m. class just so I could sit next to you.</item>
        <item>You have the moves like Jagger.</item>
        <item>You\'re so hot that you denature my proteins.</item>
        <item>All I want for Christmas is you!</item>
        <item>You are the world\'s greatest hugger.</item>
        <item>You have a perfectly symmetrical face.</item>
        <item>If you were in a movie you wouldn\'t get killed off.</item>
        <item>Your red ruby lips and wiggly hips make me do flips!</item>
        <item>I definitely wouldn\'t kick you out of bed.</item>
        <item>They should name an ice cream flavor after you.</item>
        <item>You\'re the salsa to my tortilla chips. You spice up my life!</item>
        <item>You smell nice.</item>
        <item>You don\'t need make-up, make-up needs you.</item>
        <item>Me without you is like a nerd without braces, a shoe with out laces, asentencewithoutspaces.</item>
        <item>Just knowing someone as cool as you will read this makes me smile.</item>
        <item>I would volunteer to take your place in the Hunger Games.</item>
        <item>If I had a nickel for everytime you did something stupid, I\'d be broke!</item>
        <item>I\'d let you steal the white part of my Oreo.</item>
        <item>I\'d trust you to perform open heart surgery on me... blindfolded!</item>
        <item>Nice butt! - According to your toilet seat</item>
        <item>Perfume strives to smell like you.</item>
        <item>I\'ve had the time of my life, and I owe it all to you!</item>
        <item>The Force is strong with you.</item>
        <item>I like the way your nostrils are placed on your nose.</item>
        <item>I would hold the elevator doors open for you if they were closing.</item>
        <item>Your every thought and motion contributes to the beauty of the universe.</item>
        <item>You make me want to frolic in a field.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="created_by">Created by JJ Wanda</string>
    <string name="inspired_by">Inspired by: <a href="http://complimentmachine.com">Compliment Machine</a></string>
    <string name="my_website">Check out <a href="http://jjwanda.com">my website!</a></string>
    <string name="donate"><a href="http://google.com">Buy me some hot chocolate!</a></string>
</resources>
